<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<LanguageData>

    <Moat.label>shallow moat</Moat.label>
    <Moat.description>A light perimeter defense to slow down your enemy. Can be destroyed by explosives.</Moat.description>
    
    <Shallowmoat.label>shallow moat</Shallowmoat.label>
    <Shallowmoat.Description>A light perimeter defense to slow down your enemy. Can be removed with "remove floor" tool.</Shallowmoat.Description>

    <GunComplex.label>gun complex</GunComplex.label>
    <GunComplex.description>A perimeter mounted gun is designed to work regardless if you have power or not as long as somebody is manning it. Explodes in a small radius of 1 when destroyed.</GunComplex.description>
	
    <RocketComplex.label>rocket complex</RocketComplex.label>
    <RocketComplex.description>An older class of weapon that requires manual control and reload. Fortunately, with the help of decent optics and deadly weapon blast radius its presence is still dreaded on the front lines. Explodes in a radius of 3 when destroyed.</RocketComplex.description>

    <MilitaryTurretGun.label>military grade turret</MilitaryTurretGun.label>
    <MilitaryTurretGun.description>A more powerful variant of an automated turret. Longer dual barrels provide increased range, and for greater burst. Has higher chance to explode in a radius of 4.</MilitaryTurretGun.description>

    <ShredderTurretGun.label>shredder turret</ShredderTurretGun.label>
    <ShredderTurretGun.description>Shredder turret is designed for close range. It doesn't explodes when destroyed thus making it a perfect choice for indoor defense, the only downside is that it takes more space than an ordinary variant.</ShredderTurretGun.description>

    <PrecisionTurretGun.label>precision turret</PrecisionTurretGun.label>
    <PrecisionTurretGun.description>A highly calibrated gun turret. Advanced optics allows it to deliver a single but precise shot at fairly long distances. Explodes rarely in a radius of 2.5.</PrecisionTurretGun.description>

    <BlastTurretGun.label>blast turret</BlastTurretGun.label> 
    <BlastTurretGun.description>Blast turret is designed for close range area damage, and it does so by launching a burst of 3 frag grenades. Explodes in a radius of 4.5 when destroyed.</BlastTurretGun.description>

    <VulcanCannon.label>vulcan cannon</VulcanCannon.label>
    <VulcanCannon.description>Fortified minigun tower that fires continuously, very durable but power hungry. Its tall and has long range, but due to that it can't aim under itself and can't be placed indoors. Explodes in a radius of 5.1 when destroyed.</VulcanCannon.description>
	
    <Turret_DevastatorMortarBomb.label>devastator mortar</Turret_DevastatorMortarBomb.label>
    <Turret_DevastatorMortarBomb.description>A magnetic catapult that launches plasma projectiles with greater velocity, accuracy, and much larger blast radius thanks to its burst of five shells. Does not consume shells but needs a lot of power. Watch out for a huge explosion in a radius of 10 when destroyed.</Turret_DevastatorMortarBomb.description>
	
</LanguageData>